adultartnetwork.com 2012-01-27

# Adult Art Network - Privacy Policy Statement

Privacy Policy Statement

Operators of the website (referred to herein as “Service” or “website”) can be reached via our contact form.

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscribers and members of our network of paysites. These include adultartnetwork.com, comixxxarchive.com, adultcomicsworld.com, adultcartoonzone.com, mangahq.com, hentaisexclub.com, 3dsexclub.com, hentaixxxtreme.com, toongayclub.com, digitalcomix.com, hentaidivx.com & cghotties.com and all other sites at which an hyperlink to this Policy appears and which are owned/controlled by the Service.

**This is an adults only service** that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 (21 in some locales) are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this website. This website does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18.

Notice - Use of Service by the subscriber, constitutes the subscriber's express assent to the use of personal information collected by website.

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS WEBSITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS WEBSITE.

**_What Type Information is collected?_**  
We only collect personal information from visitors to our website when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services. We may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, birth date, username and password. 

Please see our payment processor's Privacy Policy concerning collected payment information.

If the website features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the website may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the website and included in its customer database.

When a subscriber of this website requests web pages from the website's server or clicks on banners or other hypertext links, the website will automatically collect some information or data about the subscriber, including the subscriber's IP address, the information that is collected may also indicate any special preferences or requests of the subscriber; all that information and data will be collected by the website and included in its customer database.

If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the website, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the website may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database.

The website may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of Members by the use of "cookies" or other programming means - any information about Members collected by the website through the use of cookies or other programming means may be included in its customer database.

**_In What Way Do We Use Your Personal and Non-Personal Information?  
_**Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide visitors with the most personalized Web experience possible and our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. By knowing a little about our visitors, we are able to deliver more relevant content and advertisements, and provide better services. We may use information collected from visitors to our website for any of the following purposes: (1) to send visitors information and promotional materials about our company, (2) to send visitors information and promotional materials from our marketing partners and third parties (such as advertisers on our website), (3) to deliver targeted display advertisements and offers by email (by matching criteria provided by our advertisers with information collected from our visitors), (4) to contact visitors to our website when necessary, (5) to allow one-click purchases or access to proprietary content by pre-populating fields, within registration or other transaction screens, with a visitor's name, billing address, and credit or charge card information (among other things), as provided by that visitor, (6) to help diagnose problems with our server, (7) to administer our website, (8) to conduct internal reviews of our website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the website), (9) to help us better understand visitors' use of our website, and (10) to protect the security or integrity of our website. Non-personal information will be used for purposes of conducting internal reviews of the website, monitoring the website, and providing a greater online experience for our visitors.

**_Do We Disclose Your Information?  
_**We may transfer or disclose information collected from visitors to our website to our employees and independent contractors, to our parent company, subsidiaries and affiliates, and to our consultants, other business associates, and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us, or if required to do so by law. **We DO NOT disclose information we collect from our website visitors to other marketing and business companies. We DO NOT share, rent, sell, or transfer any personal information provided by our visitors to third parties**.

During the registration process, and at certain times during any member user session, we may present additional offers from third party service providers. Our third party service providers have their own terms and conditions and privacy policies. We suggest that visitors access these third party websites and review their terms and conditions and privacy policies before "subscribing" to any third party offer.

**_What Security Measures Do We Take To Protect Your Data?  
_**Consistent with the Policies set forth in this Privacy Statement, the website has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the website. **From the moment you access our join page all your data will be protected by secure encrypted connection.** Also, all communication between our server and payment processors will also be in same secure environment. 

All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the website as non-confidential, and consequently the website assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

**_Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address  
_**There may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers from the operators of the website which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers") which also might contain sexually oriented material. By joining our website(s) and/or providing your emaill, you are giving your consent and agree to receive Offers from us, with the understanding that you can opt-out of these emails at any time by following the provided "Opt-Out" Revocation procedure.

**_"Opt-Out" Revocation Procedure  
_** To opt-out of receiving marketing or other promotional communications from us, we provide you with the following options: you may (1) follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions contained in the communication from us; you may (2) visit our mailing list section to enter your email address, select Unsubscribe option and click Submit; or (3) write to us at the following address with your request: P.O. Box 27740 Las Vegas, NV 89126-7740

**_Protection of Children's Privacy_**  
We strongly support parental controls on the Internet. Our websites are not intended to be viewed by minors and self labled to support major blocking servies. If you are a parent and want to block any of our websites, please consider using one of those **free** solutions: [RTA](http://rtalabel.org/) \- [ICRA](http://www.fosi.org/icra/) \- [Safesurf](http://www.safesurf.com/) ** _Links_**  
Please also note that the owners of this website are not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of websites to which it may provide links or the websites of its advertisers.

**_Corporate Changes  
_**In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset or stock sale, bankruptcy, or other asset transfer (regardless of legal formality), any of our assets may be transferred to a third party, including personal information collected from visitors to our website.

**_How to cancel your subscription  
_**You can cancel your subscription online by visiting the Cancel Membership section of the website.

**_How can you access the information we have collected from you?  
_**Visitors who wish to access or change the information they provided to our website, should send a message to us.

**_How can you contact the website operator?  
_**Visitors who have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or their interactions with this Service, should contact us via our contact form.

 _ **Changes to this privacy policy  
**_

There may be times when we need to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. To ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices, please bookmark this page and check back often.

**_Acceptance of privacy terms & conditions  
_**By visiting this website, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting this website, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of this website. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party websites accessible through our website (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those websites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies.

Date of issuance of this release: November 08, 2009. We can be reached by our contact form for any questions.
